export const questions = [
    {
        question: "What is privacy?",
        options: ["A secret spot only on the internet", "Your ability to control access to personal space and information", "Leaving footprints online", "Public information"],
        answer: "Your ability to control access to personal space and information"
    },
    {
        question: "Why should you care about privacy?",
        options: ["It's unnecessary in the digital age", "Protects you from fraud and embarrassing situations", "Increases your online visibility", "Allows others to judge you freely"],
        answer: "Protects you from fraud and embarrassing situations"
    },
    {
        question: "What is identifiable information?",
        options: ["Breadcrumbs left online", "Non-identifiable details", "Key details like social media profiles and online purchases", "VIP section of personal data"],
        answer: "Key details like social media profiles and online purchases"
    },
    {
        question: "What are non-identifiable information?",
        options: ["Key details like social media profiles", "Online purchases", "VIP section of personal data", "Breadcrumbs online that alone may not mean much but paint a picture when combined"],
        answer: "Breadcrumbs online that alone may not mean much but paint a picture when combined"
    },
    {
        question: "What should giving consent for sharing information be?",
        options: ["An active choice – opt-in", "An automatic choice – opt-out", "Unnecessary", "Rarely done"],
        answer: "An active choice – opt-in"
    },
    {
        question: "What does public information mean?",
        options: ["Only seen by potential employers", "Information seen by everyone", "Breadcrumbs left online", "VIP section of personal data"],
        answer: "Information seen by everyone"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the significance of understanding online privacy in the real world?",
        options: ["No significance", "Helps in maintaining an active digital presence", "Helps in understanding the value of privacy in the digital age", "Increases online judgment"],
        answer: "Helps in understanding the value of privacy in the digital age"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Privacy is the same as having a secret spot only on the internet.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Your digital footprint includes the websites you visit, the things you like and share, and the searches you make.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Sensitive information should be accessible to everyone.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Consent for sharing information should be an automatic choice – opt-out.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Non-identifiable information, when combined, can paint a picture of who you are.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Every time you go online, you leave digital footprints behind.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Privacy in the digital age is unnecessary.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Giving consent for sharing information should be an active choice – opt-in.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Sensitive information is like the VIP section of your personal data - only special, trusted people or entities should have access.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Your online footprints can tell a story about you, sometimes unintentionally.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Public information is only visible to your best friend.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Privacy in the real world is unrelated to online scenarios.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Non-identifiable information alone can reveal a lot about you.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a data breach analogous to?",
        options: ["Opening a bank account", "Cracking a vault with valuables", "Purchasing online goods", "Writing a letter"],
        answer: "Cracking a vault with valuables"
    },
    {
        question: "Who can be affected by data breaches?",
        options: ["Only individuals", "Only big companies", "Everyone, including big companies, small websites, and governments", "Only governments"],
        answer: "Everyone, including big companies, small websites, and governments"
    },
    {
        question: "What is surveillance in the context of privacy risks?",
        options: ["Watching someone with their knowledge", "Collecting bits of digital behavior over time to create a profile without the individual’s consent", "Public safety awareness", "Only government monitoring"],
        answer: "Collecting bits of digital behavior over time to create a profile without the individual’s consent"
    },
    {
        question: "Why is identity theft a concern for children as well?",
        options: ["They have less valuable information", "Children's identities are a clean slate", "Children are not targeted for identity theft", "They are protected by law"],
        answer: "Children's identities are a clean slate"
    },
    {
        question: "How do free apps and services often utilize your data?",
        options: ["They encrypt it for security", "They use it to enhance user experience", "They collect and sell it to advertisers", "b and c"],
        answer: "They collect and sell it to advertisers"
    },
    {
        question: "What are cookies in the context of privacy risks?",
        options: ["Physical objects used for tracking", "Digital breadcrumbs that websites use to remember you", "Passwords for online accounts", "Tracking devices installed on your computer"],
        answer: "Digital breadcrumbs that websites use to remember you"
    },
    {
        question: "What is one of the purposes of cookies on websites?",
        options: ["To remember your favorite recipes", "To remember login details", "To play games online", "To track your physical location"],
        answer: "To remember login details"
    },
    {
        question: "What is phishing in the context of privacy risks?",
        options: ["A type of fishing sport", "Scammers pretending to be legitimate to obtain personal info", "A form of digital currency", "A method of secure online communication"],
        answer: "Scammers pretending to be legitimate to obtain personal info"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Data breaches can only happen to big companies.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Surveillance is primarily about watching someone without their knowledge without collecting bits of digital behavior.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "True/False: Identity theft recovery is a quick and simple process.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Unwanted data collection is solely about information you type into forms.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Cookies are only used for remembering login details.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "All tracking, including cookies, is considered bad for privacy.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Scams are always easy to detect and recognize.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Free apps and services never collect and sell user data to advertisers.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Identity theft is a risk only for adults.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Unwanted data collection includes information like IP addresses and device IDs.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "Surveillance is always done with blatant signs, so individuals are aware it's happening.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Phishing is analogous to legitimate digital communication.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Cookies can make your life easier but do not involve tracking.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a passphrase?",
        options: ["A sequence of numbers", "A sequence of words or a sentence", "A combination of symbols and letters", "Your birthdate"],
        answer: "A sequence of words or a sentence"
    },
    {
        question: "It is advisable to use the same password across multiple sites for easier memorization.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Text messages are the most secure form of Two-Factor Authentication.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Why is using an app or a physical token recommended for 2FA?",
        options: ["They are easier to set up", "They are more secure than text messages", "They are cheaper", "They work without an internet connection"],
        answer: "They are more secure than text messages"
    },
    
    {
        question: "Before posting anything online, it is important to consider the potential future consequences.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "True"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of teaching friends and family about online privacy?",
        options: ["To increase your social media following", "To make them aware of potential risks", "To impress them with your knowledge", "To get more likes on your posts"],
        answer: "To make them aware of potential risks"
    },
    {
        question: "Privacy settings on new apps and social platforms are often set to share less by default.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    
    {
        question: "Why is it important to actively choose privacy settings?",
        options: ["To increase social media engagement", "Defaults are often set to share more", "It's a requirement by law", "It saves time"],
        answer: "Defaults are often set to share more"
    },
    {
        question: "Reading the terms and conditions is unnecessary as they don't impact your privacy.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Data encryption is like sending personal letters without any code.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    
    {
        question: "How can you ensure your connection to a website is encrypted when browsing online?",
        options: ["Look for 'http://' in the web address", "Look for a padlock icon in the address bar", "Check the website's privacy policy", "Use a virtual private network (VPN)"],
        answer: "Look for a padlock icon in the address bar"
    },
    {
        question: "Regularly updating your software is not necessary for maintaining privacy.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "Using reputable antivirus and anti-malware software is unnecessary for privacy protection.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "What is an analogy given for data encryption?",
        options: ["Sending a postcard", "Sending a letter without an envelope", "Sending a letter written in a code that only the intended recipient can understand", "Sending a letter with a tracking device"],
        answer: "Sending a letter written in a code that only the intended recipient can understand"
    },
    {
        question: "It is advisable to keep your passwords simple and easy to remember.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the primary purpose of Two-Factor Authentication?",
        options: ["To make login processes faster", "To add an extra layer of security", "To replace passwords", "To track user behavior"],
        answer: "To add an extra layer of security"
    },
    {
        question: "Why is it important to consider the impact on your job prospects or personal relationships before posting online?",
        options: [
            "To increase social media followers",
            "To impress friends and family",
            "Future consequences and privacy",
            "It has no impact on personal life"
        ],
        answer: "Future consequences and privacy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the recommended action if a company changes its privacy policy?",
        options: [
            "Ignore the change",
            "Delete your account",
            "Stay informed and understand the impact",
            "Complain to the company"
        ],
        answer: "Stay informed and understand the impact"
    },
    {
        question: "Using the same password for multiple sites is a good practice for memorization.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the significance of the 'https://' in a web address?",
        options: [
            "It indicates a secure, encrypted connection",
            "It stands for 'highly trusted server'",
            "It is a website's ranking indicator",
            "It is a type of internet protocol"
        ],
        answer: "It indicates a secure, encrypted connection"
    },
];